Guide to the Edward Weber Allen Papers 1886-1975
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Personal Papers, 1929-1975
  - General Correspondence
    Association of Pacific Fisheries, 1933, 1934, 1964, 1965, 1968
    Baird, Roger A., 1961
    Bartlett, Edward Lewis, 1957, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966
    Bartlett, Glen C., 1933
    Barton, Bruce, 1939
    Bates, William C., 1960
    Bauer, Harry C., 1948, 1951, 1953, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1959, 1962, 1966
    Beals, Walter B., 1929, 1931, 1934, 1961
    Beans, George H., 1951, 1954, 1959, 1963
    Bell, Frank T., 1935
    Bender, Robert, 1933, 1934, 1935
    Bennett, Eugene D., 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1961, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968
    Berner, Richard C., 1962, 1966, 1967, 1969
    Best, John S., 1956, 1960, 1967, 1968, 1969
    Bettis, M. Gary, 1968, 1969
    Bingham, Joseph Walter, 1932, 1957, 1960, 1962, 1964, 1968
    Birdseye, Story, 1971
    Bishop, Homer, 1935
    Bishop Jr., William W., 1955, 1957, 1958, 1960, 1965, 1966, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971
    Blackiston, Henry, C., 1957
    Blake, Bruce, 1932, 1934
    Blakemore, Thomas L., 1953, 1954, 1956, 1957, 1968, 1969
    Blethen, Clarence, 1931, 1932
    Blethen, Frank A., 1958
    Boettiger, John, 1939, 1940
    Bohemian Grove, 1946
    Boldt, George H., 1962
    Bondy, G. O. A., 1932, 1933, 1935, 1936
    Bone, Homer T., 1940
    Bourne, C. B., 1960, 1963, 1966
    Boyd, Homer L., 1954
    Braden, Spruille, 1946
    Brady, Hugh P., 1932, 1964, 1966, 1970
    Braman, James D., 1964, 1965, 1968
    Brewer, Robert P. 1967
    Bricker, John W., 1956, 1958
    Brittin, Burdick H., 1966, 1971
    Brooding, Milton E., 1955, 1957, 1958, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1971
    Buchanan, J. M., 1956, 1957, 1961, 1964
    Buchanan, Richard W., 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1929
    Buckley Jr., William F., 1955, 1970, 1971
    Bundy, F. M., 1959
    Burke, William T., 1966, 1967
    Burner, Clifford J.
    Bush, George B., 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934
    Butcher, L. G. B., 1964
    Campbell, Ernest W., 1961
    Campbell, Fred E., 1962, 1964, 1967
    Canada, Dept. of Fisheries, 1933, 1934
    Canada, Prime Minister B.C., 1939
    Canada, Provincial Fisheries Dept., 1934
    Carlson, Maxwell, 1961
    Carlson, Ted. D., 1959
    Chadwick, S. F., 1933
    Chamber of Commerce, Bellingham, 1958, 1960
    Chamber of Commerce, Juneau, 1933
    Chamber of Commerce, Seattle, 1929, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1951, 1958, 1960, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1971
    Chamber of Commerce, Tacoma, 1935
    Chamber of Commerce, U.S., 1933
    Chapman, Wilbert McLeod, 1949, 1957, 1958, 1967, 1968
    China Club of Seattle, 1931, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1955, 1960, 1961, 1965, 1970
    Chopnich, Max, 1964, 1969
    Church, J. E., 1934, 1935
    Clapp, Norton, 1960
    Clark, Donald H., 1956
    Clark, George R., 1960, 1961, 1962
    Clark, Henry W., 1951, 1956
    Clark, Irving M., (d.1960), 1931, 1954, 1961
    Clark, J. A., 1957
    Clarke, Fred, 1933
    Clark, George R., 1955
    Clinton, Gordon, 1962
    Clise, Chas. P., 1955, 1956
    Clise Jr., James W., 1933, 1935
    Cole, William, 1933, 1934
    Colclough, 0. S. 1958, 1959
    Collier, William B., 1971
    Comstock, George K., 1934
    Conway, Ray, 1931, 1932, 1956, 1968
    Cordon, Guy, 1954
    The Cosmos Club, 1934, 1958, 1961, 1970, 1971
    Council, Mary Lee, 1962
    Crawford, Phillips M., 1956, 1957
    Curtis, Asahel, 1932, 1934
    Davies, Raymond C., 1953
    Day, Albert M., 1958
    Dean, Anthony P., 1969
    Dean, Arthur H., 1960, 1972
    Delta Chi, 1932, 1934, 1935, 1962
    DeLucien, Ronald W., 1964, 1965, 1967, 1968
    Dempsey, Edward V., 1932, 1933
    Deutsch, Eberhard P., 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971
    Dill, C. C., 1931
    Dimond, Anthony J., 1932, 1933, 1934
    Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1958
    Donohoe, H. E., 1936
    Donovan, William J., 1949, 1957
    Donworth, Carl, 1933, 1934
    Dougherty, J. Chrys, 1960
    Driscoll, John Gerald, 1962, 1968
    Dulles, John Foster, 1947, 1951
    Dunbar, John, H., 1929, 1932
    Dunlop, H. A., 1956, 1961
    Duvall, Donald K., 1970
    Earoes, A. W., 1948
    Eastwood, E. 0., 1934
    Francis Edward Ltd., 1932, 1935, 1936, 1951, 1955, 1956, 1968
    Egan, William A., 1959, 1962, 1965
    Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1957
    Eisenhower, Edgar N., 1954
    Ely, Northcutt, 1966, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971
    Essery, Carl V., 1932, 1951
    Evans, Daniel, B., 1966
    Everest, H. P., 1948, 1952
    Explorers Club, 1954, 1956, 1958, 1962, 1965
    Explorers Journal, 1957, 1967, 1970, Eyerdam, Walter J., 1971
    Fairchild, Wilma B., 1958, 1959, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964
    Far East Society of Seattle, 1933, 1935
    Parley, John L., 1954, 1956
    Farwell, George, W., 1967
    Fellows of the American Bar Foundation, 1970
    Finch, George A., 1933
    Finley, Robert C., 1961
    Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1931, 1955
    Fisheries Council of Canada, 1960
    Fishing Vessel Owners Association, 1967
    Fletcher, Robert H., 1959, 1960, 1972
    Flory, William E., 1947, 1948
    Folsom, Victor C., 1957, 1960, 1961, 1968
    Fong, Hiram L., 1970, 1971
    Force, H. C., 1933, 1934
    Foss, Henry, 1965
    Foster, Frank H., 1931
    Foster, Linn B., 1957, 1959
    Found, William A., 1933
    Frankland, Charles F., 1934, 1958
    Frayn, R. Mort, 1969
    Freeman, Miller, 1932, 1953, 1936, 1954, 1955, 1966
    Priele, Haakon B., 1933, 1934, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971
    Priele, Harold B., 1959, 1961, 1969, 1970
    Friggens, Paul, 1961
    Proude, Edward R., 1933
    Fuller, Richard E., 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1952, 1954, 1955
    Furlony, Charles W., 1960, 1962
    Gabrielson, Ira N., 1947, 1958, 1961
    Gallagher, Leo, 1963
    Gallagher, Marion G., 1962, 1966, 1969, 1972
    Gandy, J. E., 1956, 1957
    Gates, Charles M., 1957
    Geraghty, J. M., 1933
    German, B. H., 1932
    Gibbs, Jim, 1957, 1972
    Gilbert, DeWitt, 1931, 1956, 1957, 1963, 1965
    Gilbert, John R., 1968, 1969
    Gillam, Stanley S. 1960, 1962
    Goddard, Wynn, 1935
    Godfrey, Joe, 1966
    Goldie, L. F. E., 1968, 1969
    Goldwater, Barry, 1970
    Goodrich, Edgar J., 1958
    Goodrich, Ernest P., 1932
    Goodrich, Herbert F., 1931, 1934, 1935, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1961, 1962
    Goodwin, William B., 1935
    Gordon, Sid W., 1953
    Gore, Lestor 0., 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1956, 1957
    Gose, T. P., 1934
    Gould, Carl P., 1933, 1960
    Green Jr., Joshua, 1957
    Gregory, Donald M., 1949, 1956
    Gregory, Tappan, 1960
    Grey, Wheeler, 1960, 1961, 1972
    Grinstead, Loren, 1933
    Gruble, Edward J., 1969
    Gruenewald, Arthur H., 1959
    Gunther, Erna, 1931, 1932
    Gustison, Sutton, 1954, 1956, 1961, 1962, 1963
    Haas, Charles T., 1935, 1939, 1960
    Hager, Roger T., 1960, 1962
    Haldane, W. H. M., 1960
    Haight, George W., 1969, 1971
    Halsey, H. R., 1932, 1933, 1961, 1966, 1969, 1970, 1971
    Hardgrove, George P., 1956
    Harley, Herbert, 1932, 1935
    Harris, C. C., 1933
    Harris, Joseph P., 1933, 1934, 1936
    Harrison, Frank, 1929, 1958, 1959, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1971
    Hatfield, Mark 0., 1966
    Haydon, John M., 1958, 1960, 1966
    Hazeltine, E. T., 1958
    Hazeltine, F. A., 1933
    Hazard, Joseph T., 1932, 1954, 1956, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1965
    Hayes, Ribert C., 1961
    Healy, Tim, 1935, 1947
    Heighway, Arthur J. Publications, 1964, 1967
    Heintzleman, Benjamin Frank, 1934, 1954, 1955, 1958, 1962, 1964
    Henning, Robert A., 1959, 1960
    Henry, Edward E., 1971
    Herrington, William C., 1947, 1950, 1952, 1957, 1959, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1968, 1969, 1960
    Herter, Christian A., 1948, 1949, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958
    Hess, Lynde W., 1956
    Hewen, H. W. B., 1932, 1935, 1936
    Hewitt, Daniel J., 1967
    Hickel, Walter J., 1969
    Hilen, Rube, 1929, 1935, 1936, 1948
    Hill, Matthew W., 1934, 1935, 1955, 1956, 1959, 1961, 1965, 1968, 1969
    Hitchcock, Charles B., 1956, 1957
    Hitchman, Robert, 1956, 1957, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1966
    Hobbs, Sam, 1951
    Hodge, Walter H., 1929, 1935, 1954, 1956, 1959, 1962
    Hodge, Warren, 1934
    Holmes, Hal, 1954, 1§56, 1957, 1958
    Holstein, Robert, 1961
    Hoover, Herbert, 1946, 1951, 1957, 1958, 1962
    Hoover Jr., Herbert, 1955
    Hurst, Fred G., 1946
    Hutchinson, Samuel, J., 1967
    Hyland, J. N., 1968
    Idyll, C. P., 1962, 1964
    International Fisheries Commission, 1932, 1948
    International Law Association, 1954, 1955
    International Pacific Halibut Commission, 1961, 1966
    International Pacific Salmon Fisheries Commission, 1958, 1961, 1965, 1966, 1968
    International North Pacific Fisheries Commission, 1955, 1956, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1966, 167, 1969, 1971
    International Trade Fair, 1954
    Jackson, Charles E., 1957, 1960, 1963, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1972
    Jackson, Henry M., 1956, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971
    Jackson, Robert H., 1950
    Jackson, Roy I., 1956, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971
    Japan Consulate, Seattle, 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1963
    Japan Society of Seattle, 1931, 1933, 1955, 1961, 1965
    Johansen, George, 1956, 1958, 1960, 1963, 1965
    Johnson, Ralph W., 1960, 1961, 1962, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967
    Johnson, Robert, 1966
    Jolly, Jon B., 1968
    Jones, Harry LeRoy, 1962, 1970, 1971
    Jones, Nard, 1962
    Jones, Wesley Linsey, 1931, 1932
    Judd, Walter H., 1961, 1962
    Kask, John L., 1968
    Kasahara, Hiroshi, 1970, 1971
    Kent, Roger, 1969
    Kidd, Gerry, 1962
    Kilpatrick, Margaret Park, 1969, 1971
    Kilroy, George P., 1932
    Kinzer, P. G. 1933, 1954
    Kirby, Homer, 1931
    Kizer, B. H., 1931, 1933, 1934
    Koning, L. de, 1946
    Knight, Earle W., 1932, 1953, 1935, 1940
    Korth, Fred, 1962, 1966, 1970
    Krueger, Robert B., 1969
    Langle, Fleuriot de, 1950, 1952, 1953, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1966, 1968, 1969
    Langlie, Arthur B., 1940, 1950, 1951, 1954, 1956
    Laurelhurst Community Club, 1932, 1933, 1935, 1936
    Lavender, Robert A.,1954, 1960
    Laybourne, Lawrence E., 1960, 1961, 1963, 1968
    Leffler, Ross L., 1957
    Leib, Karl, 1929, 1932, 1933
    Leverone, Nathaniel, 1953
    Lewis, William Draper, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935
    Liberty Lobby, 1969, 1973
    Little, Herbert S., 1933, 1957
    Long, Hargrave A., 1933
    Looney, Warren F., 1957
    Lorimer, George H., 1932, 1934
    Lowe, R. E., 1934
    MacArthur, Douglas, 1949
    Macbride, Philip D., 1933
    Macfarlane, Robert S. 1933, 1934, 1957, 1960
    Mack, Russell V. 1954, 1956, 1958
    MacKintosh, Kenneth, 1929, 1932, 1933
    MacLean, J. Angus, 1957
    Maggs Brothers Ltd., 1951, 1952, 1963
    Magnuson, Warren G., 1956, 1957, 1960, 1962, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971
    Malley, Henry O., 1932
    Marine Digest, 1958
    Martin, Charles E., 1933, 1935, 1948, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1961, 1963, 1964
    Martin, Clarence D., 1933, 1934
    Martin, Dewey, 1932
    Martin, G. D., 1934
    McCarthy, William, 1961, 1962
    McCurdy, Horace W., 1946, 1958, 1960, 1961
    McDermid, W. A., 1931, 1932, 1954, 1955, 1959
    McDevitt, Joseph B., 1964, 1968, 1969, 1970
    McDonald, Donald A., 1933
    McDonald, Lucile, 1962
    McGinnis, Fred P., 1962, 1963, 1967, 1969
    McGowan, John S., 1963, 1968
    McKernan, Donald L., 1956, 1958, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971
    McKinlay, John, 1947, 1949
    McLaughlin, Frank, 1961, 1962
    McSpadden, George E., 1953, 1958, 1961
    Meacham, Charles H., 1968, 1969
    Meany, Edmond S., 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934
    Meisnest, Darwin, 1931
    Mergentheim, Morion A., 1932
    Milczewski, Marion A., 1960, 1961, 1962, 1966, 1967, 1970
    Millard, William J., 1929, 1933, 1934, 1935
    Miller, Keith, 1968
    Miller, Justin, 1933, 1934
    Miller, Robert C., 1960, 1964, 1965, 1966
    Mills, Edith, 1933
    Mitchell, Hugh B. 1949, 1952
    Monroe, Robert D., 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1970
    Montana Historical Society, 1965, 1966, 1970, 1971, 1972
    Moores, Ben C., 1966
    Morris, J. Malcolm, 1953, 1954, 1956
    Morse, Wayne L., 1934, 1946, 1947, 1949, 1954, 1959
    Motherwell, J. A., 1934
    The Mountaineers, 1934, 1957, 1958, 1960, 1965
    Municipal League of Seattle and King County, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1954, 1958
    Murdock, James Oliver, 1958, 1966, 1969
    Murphy, Arthur A., 1933, 1934
    Murphy, Robert D., 1956
    Nakat Packing Corporation, 1931, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1956
    National Canners Association, 1958, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972
    National Federation of Fishermen, 1971
    The National Fish Meal Oil Association, 1968, 1969
    National Fishermen Wives Inc., 1969
    National Parks Committee, 1934
    National Planning Association, 1969
    The Nature Conservancy, 1966
    Neblett, William R., 1958, 1962, 1964
    Nelson, Frederic, 1953, 1954, 1957
    Nelson, Richard I., 1966, 1969, 1972
    Neville, William C., 1959, 1963, 1966
    Nishi, Toshio, 1967
    Nixon, Richard M., 1949
    O'Connor, Matthew, 1954, 1957
    Oda, Shigeru, 1960, 1962, 1964, 1968
    Odegaard, Charles E., 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1965, 1970
    Odiin, Reno, 1959
    Oriental Art Committee, 1931, 1932
    O'Rorke, Martin, J., 1959, 1962, 1964, 1966
    Ozere, S. V., 1961, 1963, 1964, 1965
    Pacific Northwest Trade Association, 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969
    Pagam, Francisco A., 1966, 1967
    Page, Don, 1963, 1964, 1966, 1970, 1971
    Paget, King, 1956
    Patterson, Tom S., 1933, 1934
    Pattullo, T. D., 1939
    Patty, Ernest N., 1955, 1959
    Patty, Stanton Ho, 1968
    Pautzke, Clarence F., 1968, 1969, 1970
    Peaslee, Amos J., 1948, 1954, 1958, 1959
    Pelly, Thomas M., 1954, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968
    Phi Gamma Delta, 1936
    Phister, Montgomery, 1953, 1954, 1955, 1957, 1960
    Pierrot, George P., 1957, 1960
    Polk, Forrest R., 1949
    Pollock, David, 1931, 1932, 1934, 1935
    Potts, Ralph B., 1968
    Powell, Charles L., 1934
    Pownall, P. C., 1970
    Pratt, Robert Y., 1933
    Prosecuting Attorneys' Association, 1934
    Puget Sound Maritime Historical Society, 1964, 1966
    Puget Sound Maritime Press Association, 1957, 1959
    The Rainier Club, 1954, 1955
    Rasmuson, Elmer E., 1969, 1971
    Re, Edward D., 1962, 1969
    Reed, Tom, 1929, 1962
    Reid, Thomas, 1956, 1957, 1958
    Republican Committee - King County, 1935
    Rhyne, Charles S., 1963
    Rice, Thomas D., 1961
    Rice, Warren C., 1948
    Rietze, Harry L., 1970
    Roberts, Elliott B., 1962, 1963, 1964, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971
    Robertson, R. E., 1932, 1933
    Rogers, Reid, 1968, 1969
    Rose, Leonard, 1966, 1968, 1969, 1970
    Rosellini, Albert D., 1959
    Ross, Bert C., 1935
    Rotary Club of Seattle, 1933, 1958,
    Rotary Club of Bellingham, 1936
    Rotary Club of Vancouver Canada, 1947
    Roy, Bruce Le, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1967, 1968, 1971
    Royal, Loyd A., 1953, 1955, 1958, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1972
    Royce, William F., 1963, 1969
    Rudkin,Charles N., 1956, 1966, 1967, 1968
    Ruff, W. F. Van, 1933
    Rupp, John N., 1954, 1956, 1959, 1966
    Rhyne, Charles S., 1957, 1958
    Sandoz, Tom P., 1956, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1963, 1964, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971
    Salisbury, Stuart M., 1958
    Saltonstall, Leverett, 1958, 1960
    Savidge, dark V., 1932, 1933
    Sawyer, E. W., 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1970
    Schaefer, Milner B., 1969
    Schaffner, Walter, 1932, 1934, 1935
    Schmitz, Dietrich, 1932, 1956
    Schmitz, Henry, 1955
    Schoettler, Robert J., 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1963
    Schwellenbach, Lewis Baxter, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1947
    Schoettler, Robert J., 1956, 1960
    Schweppe, Alfred J., 1931
    Seattle Art Museum, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1951, 1952, 1954, 1972
    Seattle Bar Association, 1929, 1931, 1934
    Seattle City Council, 1968
    Seattle Committee on Foreign Relations, 1970, 1971
    Seattle Historical Society, 1952, 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1966, 1968
    Seattle-King County Bar Association, 1967
    Seattle, P.-I., 1967, 1969
    Seattle Public Library, 1931, 1932
    Seattle Ski Club, 1933, 1934, 1935
    The Seattle Times, 1963, 1966
    Selvidge, Lew, 1961
    Senior, C. N. 1954, 1960, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970
    Seymour, North, 1960
    Shepherd, Harold, 1931, 1933, 1934, 1935
    Sherwood, Cameron, 1968
    Shiels, Archibald W., 1933, 1934, 1955, 1956, 1966
    The Shorey Book Store, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1972
    Sieg, Lee Paul, 1934
    Sledd, Jim B., 1964, 1965
    Smith, Charles L., 1934, 1935
    Smith, Charles Wesley, 1931, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936
    Snedden, C. W., 1961
    Snohomish County Bar Association, 1931
    Sons of the American Revolution, 1929, 1931, 1934, 1960, 1961
    Spector, Ivan, 1931
    Sproul, Robert G., 1947, 1957, 1958
    Steele Jr., G. E., 1959, 1960, 1962, 1965
    Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1949, 1953, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1963
    Henry Stevens, Son Stiles, 1956, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1967
    Stevens, Stoddard M., 1963
    Steveson, John R., 1969, 1970, 1975
    Stinson, Bill, 1964
    Stone, Edward T., 1961
    Stone, Kirk H., 1947, 1954, 1959, 1965
    Storey, Robert G., 1957
    Story, Robert C., 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959
    Stotler, F. L., 1931
    Streeter, Daniel D., 1957, 1960
    Sturgeon, Leo D., 1947, 1954, 1956, 1957
    Sundstrom, Amos, 1936
    Suzuki, Kyuhei, 1961, 1965, 1966
    Suzzallo, Henry, 1932, 1933
    Swygard, Kline R., 1958, 1961, 1956, 1967
    Tarrant, S. G., 1959, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1968
    Taylor Jr., C. W., 1954, 1955
    Taylor, Francis William, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1962
    Taylor, Roger C., 1966
    Terry, William M., 1970, 1971
    Thiele, Karl, 1931, 1932, 1933
    Thomas, Christy, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1962
    Thompson, Charles M., 1935, 1936, 1954
    Thompson, Dean, 1931
    Thompson, Kenneth W., 1956
    Thompson, W. P., 1931, 1958, 1959, 1960
    Todd Jr., J. W., 1961, 1963, 1966, 1972
    Tollefson, Thor C., 1956, 1957, 1958, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963
    Toussaint, A., 1950, 1951
    Troy, John W., 1933
    Truman, Harry S., 1951
    Tubb, J. A., 1956, 1965, 1966
    Turlington, Edgar, 1946, 1957, 1958
    Tuttle, Charles E., 1935, 1936, 1957, 1959, 1967, 1971
    Uhlman, Wes C., 1969
    Underwood, J. J., 1932, 1933, 1935, 1936
    United Nations Food Agriculture, 1963
    United Nations Law of the Sea, 1958
    United States Interior Dept., 1931, 1932, 1957
    United States Justice Dept., 1959
    United States State Dept, 1938, 1939, 1951, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970
    United States Intelligence, 1948
    United States Maritime Commission, 1939
    United States Naval Institute, 1956, 1963, 1966
    University of Washington Alumni Association, 1929, 1931, 1934, 1952, 1960
    University of Washington Associated Students, 1929, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1957
    University of Washington Business Administration College
    University of Washington Fisheries College, 1960, 1963, 1965, 1966, 1968, 1970
    University of Washington International Affairs Institute, 1958, 1959
    University of Washington Law Library, 1956, 1963, 1964, 1969, 1971
    University of Washington Law School, 1931, 1933, 1934, 1960, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966
    University of Washington Library, 1931, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1948, 1951, 1960, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1972
    University of Washington Political Science Dept., 1932, 1933, 1935, 1963
    University of Washington Regents, 1933
    Vail, R. W. G., 1932, 1934, 1952, 1955, 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960
    Van Cleve, Richard A., 1956, 1957, 1960, 1963, 1965, 1966, 1970
    Vanderbilt, Arthur T., 1955, 1956
    Vanderbilt, William, 1969
    Villadolid, D. V., 1948, 1953
    Wade, Hugh Joseph, 1959, 1961, 1962, 1963
    Wakefield, Lowell, 1962, 1963
    Walker, Robert E., 1956
    Washington Athletic Club, 1931
    Washington Attorney General., 1929, 1932, 1969
    Washington Fisheries Dept., 1956, 1959
    Washington Parks and Recreation Commission, 1933
    Washington Secretary of State, 1965
    Washington State Patrol, 1933, 1934
    Washington State Bar Association, 1929, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1964, 1965
    Washington State Federation of Commercial Organizations, 1935
    Washington State Historical Society, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1971
    Washington State International Trade Fair, 1960, 1965
    Washington State Trade Fair, 1957
    Way, Griffith, 1954, 1968, 1972
    Wedin, John, 1960, 1962, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1971, 1972
    Wemer, H. O., 1956, 1957, 1960
    West Coast Foreign Trade Group, 1959
    Western Fisheries, 1961, 1967, 1968
    Westland, Jack, 1954, 1957, 1958
    Wheat, Carl I., 1932, 1934
    Wickersham, James, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936
    Wiley, Alexander, 1953
    Williams, W. Walter, 1954, 1955, 1956
    Wilkins, William J., 1952
    Willkie, Wendell L., 1941
    Willoughby, William R., 1966
    Winkenwerder, Hugo, 1933
    Winn, Grover C., 1931, 1935
    Wisconsin Historical Society
    Witherspoon, Herbert, 1933
    Women's City Club, 1956, 1958
    Wood, H. S., 1929, 1935
    Wood, Robert L., 1968
    Wright, Charles T., 1964
    Yarborough, Ralph, 1957
    Yonker, Walter, 1965, 1968, 1969
    Young, J. Arthur, 1955, 1956, 1957, 1959, 1966, 1967
    Young, James R., 1934, 1962, 1968, 1969
    - 1929 (Box 27)
    - 1931-June 1957 (Box 28)
    - July 1957-1971 (Box 29)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 30)
  - General Correspondence -- Unsorted, undated (Box 30)
  - General Correspondence Regarding:
    - Dancing Trails, 1951-1954 (Box 30)
    - North Pacific, 1937 (Box 30)
    - Law Review Articles and Alaska Life, 1946 (Box 30)
    - Articles, 1943-1972 (Box 30)
    - Snow Mountain Apples, 1945-1946 (Box 30)
  - General Correspondence
    - Moran, Robert, 1926-1933 (Box 30)
    - Wisconsin State University Alumni Association, circa 1967-1972 (Box 30)
    - University of Chicago and University of Washington Alumni, 1933-1934, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Incoming Letters
    - Paget, F. King, 1945 (Box 30)
    - Landon, Alf. M., 1943 (Box 30)
  - Outgoing Letters, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Lists, 1964-1967 (Box 30)
  - Addresses, undated (Box 30)
  - Writings
    - The Vanishing Frenchman, Mysterious Disappearance of Lapérouse: Manuscripts, Correspondence, and Research Materials (Box 31-32)
    - North Pacific, 1936 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, Notes, Fragments, undated (Box 32)
    - Book Reviews, undated (Box 32)
    - "Benyowski", undated (Box 32)
    - "On to Washington", undated (Box 32)
    - "To Hell with the Army", undated (Box 32)
    - "Two Guns and Old Montana", undated (Box 32)
  - Writings -- Poems, undated (Box 32)
  - Student Work, undated (Box 32)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 32)
  - Speeches, undated (Box 32)
  - Clippings -- Writings by Allen, undated (Box 32)
  - Publications
    - Containing Articles by Allen, undated (Box 33)
    - Dancing Tails, undated (Box 33)
  - Writings of Others, undated (Box 33)
  - Publications -- Articles About Allen, undated (Box 33)
  - Subject Files
    - Alaska International Highway, undated (Box 33)
    - Allen Honors, undated (Box 33)
    - Anian, Island of California, Jesso, undated (Box 33)
    - Directory, undated (Box 33)
    - Glacier Bay, Alaska, undated (Box 33)
    - Joseph T. Hazard, "Our Granted Lands for Public Schools", undated (Box 33)
    - Harold Ickes and Alaska, undated (Box 33)
    - Japan, undated (Box 33)
    - Maps, undated (Box 33)
    - Montana, undated (Box 33)
    - Publicity of Crime (Box 33)
    - Santa Ana, undated (Box 33)
    - Seattle Public Library, 1931-1932 (Box 33)
    - Washington State Parks, undated (Box 33)